ADRIJAN SULEJMANOV

SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Goal-oriented software developer with 8 years of indepth experience at web and mobile app development.

I have experience working at various companies as a software developer where I primarily write with Javascript and build recommendation systems along with learning from the best and the brightest. I also have experience working at a big data startup. I am the type of person who absorbs insights from others easily as well as freely shares mine.

CONTACT INFORMATION

lLinkedin: linkedin.com/in/adrijan-s-571345206 Email: andrysoul32@gmail.com Website: andriicv.herokuapp.com/ Skopje, Skopski, North Macedonia

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Full Stack Developer

NUMBERX JAN 2018 - APR 2021

- Upgraded our jQuery-based financial dashboard to React App.
- Used Redux as a state management and Added customized charts for currency exchanging with D₃
- Developed reusable React components which can be used by other developers and other areas of the application.
- Built distributed backend structure for each service with Node
- Added user validations and user permissions by using Node.JS.
- Designed database structure using Type ORM and integrated with each service (MySQL) $\,$

Full Stack Developer

TGM RESEARCH FEB 2017 - DEC 2017

- Developed PHP-based server-side API using Laravel framework and implemented MVC architecture.
- Developed an internal Laravel application to track customers' shipment history and to customize every shipment to individual customers based on their profile selections and previous orders.
- Developed survey statistics logic and implemented an AI engine to track user experiences
- Optimized the project and improved the speed of the project with MySQL

Full Stack Developer

CONSALTA MAR 2014 - DEC 2016

- Developed different cloud based analytics enterprise products with Angular 4
- Created shared modules, components that could be shared across the components application.
- Handled and build multiple asynchronous service calls using RxJS such as Observables, behavior subjects and some of its operators.

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

American College Skopje

COMPUTER SCIENCE 2010 - 2014

CORE SKILLS

- Back-end

Node, Express, Fastify, Hapi, Nest, Yii2, Laravel, Flask

- Front-end:

Angular 2+, Angular Universal, React, Next.js, Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Vue3

- Others

Autho, Keycloak, OAuth

Facebook Graph API, Facebook Marketing API, Google AdWords API, Google Analytics, Twitter, Stripe